Guide to the John W. Shenk Papers, 1900-1935
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - S - GENERAL IN (I). (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SHENK, JOHN WESLEY (1875 - 19), including letters to the following persons:
      - Unidentified., (6) (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - - T - (Box 10, Folder 16)
          - Tally, Dorothy., '22
          - Tappaan, Claire S., '27
          - Taylor, A. B., '24
          - Taylor, B. Grant., '23
          - Taylor, David G., '20
          - Taylor, Horace N., '13-'29
          - Teel, Courtney A., '31
          - Thelen, Max., '30-'35
          - THOMAS, LEONARD E., '24-'34; (13) (Box 10, Folder 17)
          - Thomas, Logan., '28
          - Thomas, W. Perry., '24
          - Thompson, Ira F., '26-'32; (5)
          - Tichenor, A. K., '34; (2)
          - Tillman, Gilmore., '35
          - Times Mirror Company., '28-'29; (3)
          - Tingley, Katherine., '27
          - Tobin, R. M., '33
          - Tomblin, M. Marie., '29
          - Torres, Josephine., '20
          - Tramutolo, Chauncey., '35
          - Travelers Insurance Company., nd '27
          - Treat, Fred A., '28
          - Tremain, Mrs. H. C., '22
          - Tribit, Charles H., '24-'29; (5)
          - Trowbridge, Delger., '33
          - [Tucker, La Vella]., '32
          - Tucker, Nathan., '33
          - Dr. Nathan Tucker Laboratory., '33
          - Tufts, C. A., '28
          - Tuller, Walter K., '24-'29; (4)
          - Turlock Irrigation District., '21
          - Turlock Lumber Company., '26
          - Turney, Raymond I., '26
          - Tuttle, Raglan., '29-'31
          - Tyler, John F., '23
        - - U - (Box 11, Folder 1)
          - Underwood, Alex R., '24
          - Underwood, Mrs. Alex R., '30
          - Union Automobile Insurance Company., '23-'31; (13)
          - Union League Club., '22
          - Union Title and Trust Company., '08
          - United States, Government of the:
            - Army. Adjutant General., '23
              - Ninth Corps. Commander., '26
            - Interior, Dept. Of. Bureau Of Pensions., '24
            - State, Dept. Of. Passport Division., '26
            - Treasury Department., '25
          - United States Law Review., '32
        - - V - (Box 11, Folder 2)
          - Vail, David A., '20
          - Van Allen, M. C., '24
          - Van Dyke, Will., '32; (2)
          - Van Ness, C. E., '26; (4)
          - Vargas, Cornelio D., '29-'33
          - Variel, R. H. F., '22
          - Veterans Of Foreign Wars. Gresham Post Number 8., '25
          - Vickers, Joseph W., '24; (2)
          - Vilas, Martin S., '30
          - Vose, Charles S., '20
        - - W - (Box 11, Folder 3)
          - Wachtel, J. V. Jr., '26-'27
          - Wade, Richard H., '22
          - Walcott, E. A., '26
          - Walker, David H. Jr., '30
          - Walker, W. T., '27
          - Wallace, A. J., nd
          - Wallace. Ora Champion., '26
          - Walters, R. T., '28-'31; (6)
          - Walton, C.S., '13
          - Walton, D. T., '30
          - Walton, W. W., '13
          - Ward, Weldon., '07
          - Warfield, Ida E., '07
          - Warmer, Benjamin F., '23
          - Warren, J. G., '07-'08; (5)
          - Warriner, Ernest B., '33
          - Washington, University Of. Registrar., '29
          - Waste, William E., '32-'35
          - Waste, William H.
          - Webb, U. S., '21; (2)
          - Webster, J. W., '24
          - Weeks, W. G., '26
          - Wehrle, Edward F., '24-'28
          - Weidner, Perry W., '23-'31; (6)
          - Welch, J. R., '24-'28; (3)
          - Welch, W. O.
            See Los Angeles, City Of. Tax Collector.
          - Weldon, Mrs. W. R. H., '20
          - Weller, Dana R., '20-'29
          - Wellington, F. M., '21
          - Welty, E. E., '25; (4)
          - Werner, Edwin P., '32
          - Werner, Helen M., '30-'34; (4)
          - West, Charles H., '32
          - West Publishing Company., '27-'31; (6)
          - Western Wood Preserving Company., '32
          - Westover, Myron., '24-'30; (4)
          - Weyle, Bertin A., '32
          - Wharton, L. R., '31
          - Wheat, Walter R., '13
          - Wheeler, Henry O. Jr., '26
          - Wheeler, Lucy E., '08
          - James T. White & Company., '28
          - White, Thomas P., '30
          - Whitehurst, G. A., '24
          - Whiting, Randolph V., '29-'34
          - Whitman, Mrs. Julian C., '33
          - Whitmore, John P., '31
          - Whitney, W. C., '26
          - Whittier State School., '28
          - Who's Who In California., '28
          - Who's Who In Government., '30
          - Wiel, Samuel C., '33
          - WILBUR, CURTIS D., nd, '29; (16) (Box 11, Folder 4)
          - Wilbur, Olive D., '24
          - Wild, George W., '22
          - Wilder, J. R., '31
          - Will, Arthur P., '28-'33; (4)
          - Willaman, Glenn D., '24
          - Williams, Eugene D., '32
          - Willis, Frank R., '26
          - Wilson, Emmet H., '30-'33; (3)
          - Wilson, Evelyn., '30; (2)
          - WILSON, MARY C. (sister of JWS), '27-'34; (8) (Box 11, Folder 5)
          - Wilson, Norman H., '25
          - Windham, Roy A., '33
          - Winship, Blanton., '32
          - Winter, Charles E., '25-'31; (5)
          - Wolden, Russell L., '26-'27
          - Wong, Thomas S., '20
          - Wood, John Perry., '07-'33; (5)
          - Woodhead, Florence M., '27
          - Woodill, H. B., '13
          - Woodley, Frank E., '13-'23
          - James Woods Dinner Invitation Committee., '29
          - Woods-Drury Company., '30
          - Woolf, Billie., '24
          - Woolwine, Clare., '27
          - Works, Lewis R., '24-'30; (6)
          - Wright, A. H., '23
          - Wright, Arthur., '23
          - Wright, Cleveland R.
          - Wright, Henry W., '28
          - Wright, J. Marion., '27
        - - Y - (Box 11, Folder 6)
          - Yankwich, Leon R., '27-'31
          - Yarwood, Paul., '32
          - Yglisias, F. R., '20
          - York, John M., '26
          - Yosemite Lodge., '27
          - Yosemite Park and Curry Company., '26; (2)
          - Yost, Mary.
          - YOUNG, EDWARD R., '08-'35; (19) (Box 11, Folder 7)
          - Young, G. G., '26
        - - Z - (Box 11, Folder 8)
          - Zwerner, George P., '28-'30
    - SHENK, JOHN W. Jr. (son of JWS), nd, '25-'29 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - SHENK, LENAH. (wife of JWS), nd, '18-'26; (11) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SHENK, SAMUEL. (son of JWS), '22 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - SHENK, SUSANNA C. (mother of JWS), nd, '07-'28; (33) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - SHENK, WILLIAM W. (brother of JWS), nd, '06-'33; (72) (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Shenk Property. Correspondence re properties in the Imperial Valley, California, managed by John Shenk (father of JWS) until his death in 1921), nd, '17-'28; (201) (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Shepardson, Francis W., '24
    - Sheridan, James M., '25
    - Sherry, Henry., nd
    - Shinn, Clement L., '27
    - Shoemaker, Eva H., '26
    - Shontz, Orfa Jean., '33
    - SHORTRIDGE, SAMUEL MORGAN (1861 -)., '25-'30; (3) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Shreve, Mrs. Jesse H., '24
    - Shurtleff, Charles A., '26
    - Silver Shield League., '22
    - Silverwood's Inc., '23
    - Siminoff, T., '24-'30
    - Simon, Ernest R., '27-'31; (4)
    - Simons, Seward A., '13
    - Single Tax League., '21
    - Sisson, Charles Peck (1890 -)., '30-'31; (4)
    - Sloane, William A. (1854 -)., '23-'24
    - Slosson, Leonard B., '22
  - S - GENERAL IN (II). (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Smallwood, Claude., '26; (2)
    - Smith, Mrs. C. S., '32
    - Smith, Clyde W., '25; (2)
    - Smith, Dave F., '31-'33
    - Smith, Eldora., '07; (3)
    - Smith, Frank M., '33-'34
    - Smith, Hattie., '30
    - Smith, Herman., '23
    - Smith, Josephine., '27
    - Smith, Le Roy B., '29
    - Smith, Lewis Howell (1872 -)., '31
    - Smith, Robert A. Inc., '31
    - Smith, Samuel Barnes., '23
    - Smith, William A. (1880 -)., '32-'33; (6)
    - Snider Brothers Real Estate., '20-'25; (12)
    - Snudden, B. Dudley., '24
    - Snyder, W. Cloyd., '26-'35; (13)
    - Socha, Max E., '32
    - Soliss, Albert N., '24; (2)
    - Solomon, Fred H., '29
    - Solomon, Irl., '26; (3)
    - Sonoma County Bar Association.
    - Sons of the American Revolution. California Chapter., '22-'31; (8)
    - Soroptimist Club Of Los Angeles., '32
    - Soult, M., '19; (2)
    - South Pasadena Lodge, No. 367, F.&.A.M., '20-'34; (10)
    - South Pasadena Savings Bank., '14; (3)
    - South West Political Club., '14
    - Southern California, University of:
      - Law School., '28-'34; (3)
      - Law Review., '28; (2)
    - Southern California Citizens' Committee., '23; (4)
    - Southern California Edison Company., '24
    - Southern California Oil Company., '28
    - Southern California Past Masters Association., '20
    - Southern California Rod and Reel Club., '20
    - Spalding, S. M., '27
    - Spanish Progressive Social Club., '14
    - Sparling, Maurice C., '31
    - Spates, Edwin M., '31
    - Speik, Frederick A., '24-'34; (8)
    - Spencer, Fanny Bixby., '23
    - Spicer, Charles W., '30
    - Spicer, E. H., '26
    - Springer, W. C., '24
    - Sproul, Joseph P., '27; (2)
    - Sproul, Robert G. (1891 -)., '29
    - Stack, Joseph R., nd
    - Stafford, Dailey S. (1890 -)., '23
    - Standard Mines Company.
    - Standard Oil Company Of California., '34
    - Stanford University.
      - Board Of Athletic Control., '33
      - Dean Of Women., '33
      - Law Association., '32
      - Registrar., nd
    - Stanislaus County Bar Association.
    - Stanley, Eugena B., '24
    - Stanley, William., '35; (2)
    - Stanley-DeBlois Company., '08
    - Stanton, Robert H., '30-'34
    - Stearns, G. B., '31
    - Steele, John P., '24
    - Steiger, George J., '31
    - Steiner, Fred A., '32
    - Stephens, Albert Lee (1874 -)., nd, '14-'35; (13)
    - Stephens, Jess E. (1882 -)., '24
    - Stephens, Raymond W., '26
    - Stephens, William., '11
    - [Stephenson, Dwight W.]
    - Sterling, Christine., '30
    - Sterry, Norman S., '24-'30
    - Sterry, Philip C., '27
    - Stevens, V. D., '20
    - Stevenson, Walter R., '28
    - Stillwell, J. E., '28-'33; (7)
    - Stimson, Marshall (1876 -)., '30
    - Stocking, Clark B., '24
    - Stoermer, Grace S.
      See Soroptimist Club of Los Angeles.
    - STONE, HARLAN FISKE (1872 -)., '25 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stone, Mrs. Richard T., '27
    - Strait, George S., '24
    - Strother, S. L., '33
    - Stuart, Edward A. (1888 -)., '31
    - Stung, H. A., '23
    - Sturges, Dain., '24
    - Suhr, Reta., '24
    - Sullivan, Jeremiah Francis (1857 -)., '27
    - Sun Drug Company., '22
    - Superior Court Judges Association Of California, '32
    - Surf and Sand Club., '23
    - Surr, Howard., '33
    - Susman, Leo H., '25
    - Sutherland, Nelle., '99
    - Sutton, Charles T., '31
    - Sutton, Ernest V., '24-'30; (4)
    - Swaffield, Roland G., '14-'30; (7)
    - Sweaza, Charles G., '24
    - Swedish-American Political Club Of San Francisco., '24
    - Sweet, Joseph G., '31
    - Symondson, Minnie A., nd, '26; (3)
  - T - GENERAL IN. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Taber, E. R., '14
    - Taber, J. L., '26
    - Taft, Fred H., '24-'30
    - Tally, Dorothy., '21
    - Tanquary, G. P., '31
    - Taplin, Irvin C., '31; (2)
    - Tappaan, Clair S., '27
    - Taylor, A. B., '24
    - Taylor, B. Grant., '23-'26
    - Taylor, C. W. Jr., '20; (2)
    - Taylor, David G., '20; (2)
    - Taylor, F. G., '13
    - Taylor, Horace N., '27-'35; (7)
    - Taylor, J. Clinton., '30
    - Taylor, John A., '07
    - Teel, Courtney A., '31; (2)
    - Thelen, Max (1880 -)., '26-'35; (8)
    - THOMAS, LEONARD E., nd, '22-'34; (19) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Perry., '31
    - Thomas, William Holcombe (1867 -)., '16-'30
    - Thompson, Ira F., '26-'27; (5)
    - Dr. Thudichum's Laboratory., '22
    - Tichenor, A. K., '34
    - Tillis, H. M., '14
    - Tillman, Gilmore., '35
    - Times Masonic Club., nd
    - Times-Mirror Company., '27-'29; (6)
    - Tingley, Katherine (1852 -)., '27
    - Tison, Alexander (1857 -)., '22
    - Title Insurance and Trust Company., '20-'24; (5)
    - Tomblin, M. Marie., '29-'30
    - Toohey, John Peter., '26
    - Topham, John., '10
    - Torres, Josephine., '20
    - Townsend, James Robert., '11; (2)
    - Traeger, William I., '26
    - Travelers Insurance Company., '20-'27; (6)
    - Treat, Archibald J., '30
    - Treat, Bush, & Ogden., '27
    - Tribit, Charles H. Jr., nd, '24; (5)
    - The Tribune., '13
    - Trowbridge, Delger., '33
    - Trusty, C. E., '23
    - [Trusty, Joseph]., '23
    - Dr. Nathan Tucker Laboratory., '33
    - Tufts, C. A., '28
    - Tuller, Walter K., '24-'33; (7)
    - Turlock Irrigation District., '22
    - Turney, Raymond I., '26; (2)
    - Tuttle, Raglan (1881 -)., '29-'31
    - Tyler, Keith., '22
    - Tyler, Willis O., '20-'35; (3)
  - U - GENERAL IN. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Underwood, Alex R., '24
    - Union Automobile Insurance Company., '26-'30; (9)
    - Union Labor Temple Association., '14
    - Union League Club Of Los Angeles., nd, '20-'22; (19)
    - Union League Building Corporation., '22; (3)
    - Union Oil Company Of California., '11; (2)
    - Union Rescue Mission., nd
    - United Republicans Of California., '16
    - United Spanish War Veterans.
      - Headquarters. Dept. Of California., '22
      - National Convention Committee., '22; (10)
      - Roosevelt Camp Number 9., '22; (4)
    - United States Government.
      - Department Of the Interior., '28
      - Department Of Justice., '26
      - Department Of State., '26; (2)
      - Treasury Department. Customs Service.
        See Hamilton, W. B.
    - United States Law Review., '32; (2)
    - United Veterans Of the Republic., '30
    - University Club Of Los Angeles., '25-'26
    - The Uplifters., '29
  - V - GENERAL IN. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Valentine, Frederick C., '24
    - Valentine, L. H., '31
    - Van Allen, M. C., '24
    - Van Dyke, Will., '32; (2)
    - Van Loan, Christine., '20-'21; (4)
    - Van Ness, C. E., '26; (2)
    - Van Ness, Mrs. C. E., '26
    - Vargas, Cornelio D., '29-'34; (6)
    - Veale, R. R., '32
    - Vedenoff, Nick., '22
    - Veterans Of Foreign Wars. James B. Gresham Post Number 8., nd, '20'22; (5)
      See also James B. Gresham Post No. 8.
    - Vickers, Joseph William (1890 -)., '24; (2)
    - Vilas, Martin S., '30
    - Vose, Charles S., '20
    - Vulcan Underwriters., '30
  - W - GENERAL IN (I). (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Wachtel, J. V. Jr., '24-'27; (4)
    - Wade, Richard H., '22-'24
    - Wadsworth, W. H., '27-'31
    - M. Elliott Waggaman & Co., '23-'26
    - Waite, Winifred., nd
    - Walcott, Earle Ashley (1859 -)., '24
    - Waldo, Edwin., '24
    - Walker, David H. Jr.
      See Aetna Life Insurance Co.
    - [Walker, George Winfield (1861 -)]., '32
    - Walker, W. T., '27; (2)
    - Wallace, Albert J., '24
    - Walters, R. T., nd, '28-'31; (10)
    - Walton, C. S., '13
    - Walton, Delvy., '28
    - War Savings Society., '18
    - War Veterans League. Los Angeles Post No. 1., '20
    - Ward, Mary Ina Mercer., '23
    - Warmer, Benjamin F., '23-'24
    - Warren and Will., '13
    - Warren, P. de B., nd
    - Warriner, Ernest B., '33
      See also National Conference Of Jews and Christians.
    - WASTE, WILLIAM HARRISON (1868 -)., '24-'35; (25) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Watkins, Lucy and Thomas., '05
    - Watson, George C., '22-'30; (3)
    - Waugh, Karl T. (1879 -)., '20-'25
    - Waugh, Nora B., nd
    - Webb, Arthur C., '24
    - Webb, Joseph J., '25
    - Webb, Ulysses Siegel (1864 -)., '21; (7)
    - C. F. Weber & Company., '27
    - Webster, J. W., '24
    - Wedelstaedt, George S. von., '24
    - Weeks, W. G., '26-'29
    - Wehrle, Edward F., '23-'28; (3)
    - Weidner, Perry W., '23-'32; (8)
    - Weinberger, Caspar Willard., '57
    - Weitzel, George Thomas., '27
    - Welch, C. L., nd
    - Welch, John R. (1856 -)., '24-'28; (5)
    - Weller, Dana R., '29
    - Weller, Frank C., '24
    - Wellington, F. M., '25
    - Wells, Allan Willett.
      See American Voters Association.
    - Wells, Rex., '99-'00
    - Welty, E. E., '25; (2)
    - Werner, Erwin P., '31-'32
    - Werner, Helen M., '30-'34; (4)
    - West, Charles H., '32
    - West Publishing Company., '24-'31; (12)
    - Western Union Telegraph Company., '09
    - Westover, Myron F. (1860 -)., '24-'30; (4)
    - Weyl, Bertin A., '22-'32; (4)
  - W - GENERAL IN (II). (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Wharton, L. R., '31; (2)
    - Wheeler, Henry O., '26; (2)
    - Wheeler Publishing Company., '29
    - White, Herbert E., '34
    - James T. White & Company., '24-'28; (4)
    - White, Thomas P., '30-'34; (3)
    - White, Vignolo., '21
    - Whitehead, Lewis E., '31; (2)
    - Whiteheather, George B., '22
    - Whiting, Randolph V., '20-'34; (4)
    - Whitmore, John P., '31
    - Whittier State School., '28
    - Who's Who In America., '27-'35; (6)
    - Who's Who In California., '27-'28
    - Who's Who In California State., '28
    - Who's Who In Government., '30-'32; (3)
    - Wickersham, George Woodward (1858 -).
      See: AMERICAN LAW INSTITUTE; National Commission On Law Observance and Enforcement.
    - Wiel, Samuel C., '27-'33; (3)
    - WILBUR, CURTIS D. (1867 -)., '23-'24; (6) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Wilbur, Leonard F., '24
    - Wilbur, Olive D. (Mrs. Curtis D.), nd, '24
    - Wild, George W., '22
    - Wilder, G. R., '31; (2)
    - WILL, ARTHUR PERCIVAL (1868 -)., nd, '22-'33; (20) (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Willey, Henry L., '29
    - Williams, Billie., '13-'23
    - Williams, Dorothy Manners., '33; (2)
    - Williams, Eugene D., '32
    - Williams, Florence M., '23
    - Williams, G. Edwin., nd
    - Williams, W. L., '24
    - Willis, Frank R., '22-'27; (6)
    - Wilson, Calvert.
      See Anona Gold Mining and Milling Co.
    - Wilson, Emmet Homer (1876 -)., '29-'34; (4)
    - Wilson, Evelyn (niece of JWS)., nd
    - Wilson, Leonard., '23
    - WILSON, MARY (sister of JWS)., nd, '10-34; (23) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Norman (nephew of JWS)., '25; (3)
    - Wilson, Thomas F.
    - The Woodrow Wilson Foundation. Southern California Headquarters.
    - Winburn, Oscar E., '15
    - Windham, R. A., '33
    - Winter, Charles Edward (1870 -)., '25-'32; (6)
    - William H. Wise & Company., '29
    - Woman's Advisory Committee., '22
    - The Woman's Bulletin., '13
    - Wood, Andrew Y., '27
    - Wood, John Perry., nd, '23-'33; (9)
    - Woodell, Nina E., '30
    - Woodhead, Florence M., '27
    - Woodley, Frank E., '13
    - Woodman, Frederic T., '24
    - Woolf, Billie., '24
    - Woolley, J. Earl., '25
    - Woolwine, Thomas Lee., '14-'16
    - Works, Lewis R., '08-'28; (5)
    - Wright, Arthur W., '23
    - Wright, Henry W., '28
    - Wright, J. Marion., '27; (3)
  - Y - GENERAL IN. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Yankwich, Leon R. (1888 -)., '27-'35; (5)
    - Yeomen Courier., nd
    - York, John M., '24-'26; (4)
    - Yosemite Lodge., '27
    - Yosemite Park and Curry Company., '26-'29
    - Young, Clement Calhoun (1869 -)., '26
    - YOUNG, EDWARD R., '07-'35; (21) (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Young, Milton K., '25; (2)
    - Young Men's Institute., '20
    - Young Men's Republican Club Of Los Angeles., '14; (4)
    - Young Men's Republican League Of Los Angeles County., nd; (2)
    - Young Womens Christian Association., '22
    - Youngworth, Leo V., '15
    - Yuma, Arizona. County Recorder., '07
  - Z - GENERAL IN. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Zimmerman, A., '31
    - Zwerner, George P., '20-'23
- BUSINESS CARDS AND ANNOUNCEMENTS. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- INVITATIONS. (Box 13, Folder 2, Folder 3)
- BILLS AND RECEIPTS. (Box 13, Folder 5, Folder 4, Folder 6)
- PRINTED MATTER (forms, circulars, applications, petitions, leaflets). Miscellaneous. (Box 14, Folder 1, Folder 2)
  - a) McEverlast, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 3)
- PROGRAMS. (Box 14, Folder 4)
- TICKETS. (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Membership Cards, ID Cards, Permits. (Box 15, Folder 1)
- FRAGMENTS OF NOTES BY JWS. (Box 15, Folder 2)
- OHIO WESLEYAN UNIVERSITY. Miscellaneous leaflets, forms, notes, report cards collected by JWS. (Box 15, Folder 3)
- MANUSCRIPTS BY OTHER THAN JWS: (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bird, N. J., Diary Of a Trip.
  - Shenk, Lenah, Near Neighbors (a play).
  - Memo from National Board of the Daughters of the American Revolution.
- LEDGERS. (Box Box 16)
  - a) Record kept from 1908 - 1923 by the Chief Judge of the Superior Courts, Los Angeles County, listing appeals taken from cases heard by each judge, and the number of reversals and affirmances. JWS was Chief Judge before his elevation to the Supreme Ct.
  - b) Notebook of JWS.
  - c) JWS Docket and Calendar. 1922-1923.
  - d) JWS Docket and Calendar. 1923-1924.
  - e) JWS Notarial Record Book, 1903 - 1910.
  - f) Mrs. John Shenk (Lenah Shenk) D. A. R. Notebook.
- LEGAL PAPERS (pleadings, briefs). Miscellaneous. (Box Box 17)
- PRINTED MATTER, miscellaneous. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - b) Fuller v. Counts, speeches, statements, documents. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - c) Ledger of Cases docketed for trial, Los Angeles Superior Court, Dept. 7. 1913-1921. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - d) JWS election posters (cardboard) 1914 candidacy for Superior Court. (Box 18, Folder 4)
- MINING AND PETROLEUM PROPERTIES. Correspondence, reports, maps, photographs, legal papers. (Box Box 19)
- MOONEY-BILLINGS CASE. Material on the proceedings against Thomas Mooney and Warren K. Billings, including: (Box Box 24)
  - a) newspaper clippings
  - b) legal documents
  - c) Hunt, Henry T., The Case Of Thomas J. Mooney and Warren K. Billings, Abstract and Analysis Of Record Before Governor Young, New York, National Mooney-Billings Committee, 1929.
  - d) form letters, leaflets, petitions.
- NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS.
  - nd, 1905 - 1911. (Box Box 20)
  - 1911. (Box Box 21)
  - 1911 - 1912. (Box Box 22)
  - 1912 - 1958. (Box Box 23)
- PRINTED MATTER, miscellaneous. (tearsheets, whole number periodicals, pamphlets, D.A.R. and Masonic publications.) (Box Box 25)
- PHOTOGRAPHS miscellaneous (Box Box 26)
- SCRAPBOOK (Box Box 28)
- DOCUMENTS, miscellaneous (Box Box 26)